Burroughs Corporation Records. ElectroData Division Records, 1952-1979. Finding Aid.
University of Minnesota Libraries
- Engineering Technical Memorandum (ETMs)
  - ETM 52: Standardization of Plug-ins Used by Burroughs (J.F. Kalbach), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - ETM 53: Transistor Linear-Input Logic Circuitry (M.J. Marosz), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - ETM 54: Ductile Iron; A New Type of Cast Iron ®. H. Summers), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - ETM 55: Descriptions of Packaging of Selected Existing Plug-In Circuits used by ElectroData Division (Dave Perry), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - ETM 56: Evaluation of a Magnetic Drum (J. Reese Brown, Jr.), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - ETM 57: Packaging of Circuits for new Commercial Computer Products (J. F. Kalbach), 1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - ETM 59: Description of Circuits (J.F. Kalbach), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - ETM 60: Comparison of Available RCA Ferrite Cores With Cores Now Being Used in Electrodata Products (R.C. Kinnick), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - ETM 61: Reliability Evaluation of Printer Punch (J. F. Kalbach), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - ETM 62: Preliminary Command List 2111 Input-Output Control (D.T. Kielty), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - ETM 64: Description of a 200-Volt, 5-Amphere Transistor Power Supply, drawings only (M.J. Marosz), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - ETM 65: A High Voltage, Fast Response Magnetic Amplifier Regulated Power Supply, drawings only, (M.J. Marosz), undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - ETM 67: Description of a 9-volt, 0.5 Ampere Transistor, drawings only (J.J. Marosz), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - ETM 69: Effect of preventive maintenance on reliability (J. F. Kalbach), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - ETM 70: Reliability and Performance Evaluation of System FA67 including Printer Punch (J.F. Kalbach, Tom Woods, Charles Block), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - ETM 71: A Preliminary Analysis of Unit Duty Factors of a 220 System in a Data Processing Application (G. N. Arnovick), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - ETM 72: The Permanent Magnet Plugboard (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - ETM 73: A Study of Self-Correcting Codes (Robert C. Minnick), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - ETM 75: An Analysis of Transaction Posting Rates Based on a Theoretical Model of a Parallel File Data Processing System (G. N. Arnovick and S.J. Wersan), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - ETM 76: A Table of All Four Variable Combinational Linear-Input Switching Circuits (Robert C. Minnick), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - ETM 77: Delay Time in Data Processing Systems (George Hare), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ETM 78: A Computer Monitor Circuit (M.J. Marosz), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ETM 79: 2111 Delay Line Memory (James C. Davidson), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ETM 80: The Transfluxor Crosspoint Switch (Edwin S. Lee), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ETM 81: Core Buffer Memory ®. English), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ETM 82: 2111 Monitor System (F. W. Looschen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ETM 83: Clocking Scheme for the 2111 Data Processor (Paul L. McMath Floyd W. Looschen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ETM 84: Evaluation of the Toggle Proposed for 2111 Useage (T. Bohen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ETM 85: A Preliminary Study of Inquiry Systems for Burroughs Data Processors (F. L. Fox, E. C. Hansen, R. S. Sharp), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - ETM 86: 80 Channel Operational Recorder Spacelab Model 8000A (Floyd W. Looschen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ETM 87: 2111 Power System (F. W. Looschen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - ETM 88: Methods of Implementing Linear-Input Logic (M.J. Marosz), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ETM 89: A.B.O. Pulse Generator (E.S. Lee), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ETM 90: Core Memory Drive and Selection Techniques (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - ETM 91: A Study of the Use of Waiting Lines in a Theoretical Model of a Parallel File Data Processing System (S.J. Wersan), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - ETM 94: Floxlok - A Nondestructive Memory Technique (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - ETM 103: Thin Film Magnetic Memories (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - ETM 104: Magnetic Core Memory Survey and Cost Studies (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - ETM 105: 108 109: Standard Switch (F. W. Looschen), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - ETM 107: Design Automation Report #1 (A.J. Kouba), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - ETM 110: Prototype High Speed Printer (H.M. Livingston), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - ETM 111: 3500 Clock System and Sine Wave Oscillator Design (James C. Davidson), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - ETM 112: Clock Amplifier (Robert B. English), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - ETM 113: Medium Speed Flip Flop (E.S. Lee), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - ETM 114: Design Guide for Parallel Plate Packages (L. Thomas and D. Parry), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - ETM 115: Delay Circuit (Frank Weber), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - ETM 116: 122 Comparison Delay Multi [transistorized monostable multivibrator] (Narsingh Deo), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - ETM 117: Diode configurations in the 3500 System (J.J. McGill), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - ETM 118: Neon Drives "a" and "b" (Robert L. Phillips), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - ETM 119: not there
  - ETM 120: An Experimental Approach to Magnetic Cores Under Two Modes of Operation (David G. Czarnetzki), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ETM 121: B5000 System, Circuit, and Logic Rules (John A. Karsten), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - ETM 122: IDA and CSA Parallel Adder Technique (John E. Croy), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - ETM 125: 3500 Interunit Cables (T.A. McCulloch), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ETM 126: A Linear Select Memory for Small Capacity Buffering Applications (P.L. McMath, T. J. Bohen, A. Russak), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - ETM 127: Magnetic Drum Memory (D.T. Kielty), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - ETM 129: Operation of a solid State Magnetic Counter (G.T. Shimabukuro), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ETM 130: Planar Magnetic Film Field Studies (William K. Orr, J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - ETM 131: Variable block Logic Diagram Program (C.S. Slemaker, Jr.), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - ETM 133: Trip Report to Datamatic (Griffin Paige), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - ETM 135: 1960 Computer Progress AIEE (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - ETM 136: Pulse Inductance of Magnetic Circuits (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - ETM 137: Magnetic Detent (D. Acres), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - ETM 138: Analysis of a Proposed Inquiry System (William J. Broderick), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - ETM 139: Gold Plating Evaluation (W.S. Lincoln and J.A. Sandy), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - ETM 141: Methods of Decimal-to-Binary Conversion (E .Croy), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - ETM 142: Switch I (Robert E. Packard), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - ETM 143: Hammer Actuating Mechanism for Drum Printer (Griffin Paige), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - ETM 146: Notes on the Design and Specification of Pulse Transformers (J.R. Brown, Jr.), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - ETM 148: High Speed Flip-Flops (E.S. Lee), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - ETM 149: Characteristics of Beam-X Switches in the Megacycle Range and Summary of Basic Operation (D.G. Czarnetzki), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - ETM 150: A Specification Format for Pulse Transformers (J. Reese Brown, Jr.), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - ETM 151: Distinguishing Character Point Combinations for Use in a Character Recognition Device (William K. Orr), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - ETM 152: Measurement of Small Speed Variations on Synchronous Capstans (H.F. Rayfield), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - ETM 153: High Accuracy Delay Circuit (Frank W. Weber), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - ETM 154: doldover Circuit A (Frank W. Weber), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - ETM 155: Delay Multi "B" (Frank W. Weber), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - ETM 156: 3500 System Power Supplies Systems (Floyd W. Looschen), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - ETM 157: The Effects of Capacitance in Parallel Plate Flatpac Circuits (Floyd W. Looschen), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - ETM 158: Delay Circuit "C" (Frank W. Weber), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - ETM 159: A Proposal and Preliminary concept for a High Speed Platen Printer (Griffin Paige), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - ETM 160: The Symposium on Large Capacity Memory Techniques for Computing Systems (R.A. Gleim), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - ETM 161: Evaluation and Specification of Magnetic Tape for Digital Computer Systems (R.W. Jack), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - ETM 162: Compression (C.S. Ananiades), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - ETM 163: Pulse Synchronizer (N. Deo), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - ETM 165: Driver 50-90 (E.S. Lee), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - ETM 166: A Delayed Complementing Flip-Flop (Frank W. Weber), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - ETM 167: Tape Read Delay Circuit (N. Deo), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - ETM 168: Competitive Magnetic Tape Systems (L.D. Green, R.W. Jack, D. Nesin), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - ETM 169: Parallel Plate Package Environmental Tests (G.P. Bottlik), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - ETM 173: Study of the B200/B5000 Tape Read/Write System and its Compatibility with 729 Read/Write (J. M. Bakshi), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - ETM 174: Datafile III Development Report ®. G. Groom, R. A. Gleim, Billawala, Simonsen), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - ETM 175: An Introduction to Polycarbonate Thermoplastic Resins: A Summary of G. E. Company Seminar (G. P. Bottilk), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - ETM 176: Zero Recovery Time Blocking Oscillator (John A. Karsten), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - ETM 180: Thin Film Memory Address Buffer ®. E. Packard), undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - ETM 181: Design and Reliability Review of 200 CPM Card Reader ®. G. Nordman, J. Macker), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - ETM 182: The 3500 Reel Servo System (H. Rayfield), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - ETM 184: Pinch Roll Driver (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - ETM 185: Voltage Failure Sensor (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - ETM 186: Servo and Rewind Relay Driver (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - ETM 187: General Mounting Procedure for Power-Type Semi-Conductors (J. R. Laube), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - ETM 188: End of Tape Sensor (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - ETM 189: Line ETM Terminator and Multi R.C. (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - ETM 190: Photo-Diode Measurements (Henry Merrill), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - ETM 191: Vacuum column Sensing Circuit (Harold L. Shaw), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - ETM 195: Preparation of Print Alignment Gages for Drum Printer (W. Griffin Paige), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - ETM 196: 205 Tape Transport and Dual Gap Head Evaluation ®. A. Smith) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - ETM 197: Read and Write Acceptance Level for B300 TSU's (Behr, Bakshi, Smith), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - ETM 198: An Advanced Circuit and Packaging Techniques Program for Electrodata M E Division Products (J. F. Kalbach), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - ETM 199: Computer Progress during 1962 (J. F. Kalbach) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - ETM 202: RC Timing For Multis and Strobe Circuits (Frank Weber), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - ETM 203: Effects of Information Patter and Crossfeed Suppressor on Pulse Crowding (M. I. Behr and R. A. Smith), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - ETM 204: Sources of Read and Write Errors in B200 (M. I. Behr and R. A. Smith), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - ETM 205: Kerr Magneto Optic Equipment with photo (Henry Merrill), 1962 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - ETM 207: A High Current Multi (F. W. Weber), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - ETM 208: A Summary of Hierarchical Memory Organizations (J. R. Bennett), 1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - ETM 209: A Priority System Program and Time Dependent (G. Shimabukuro), 1962 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ETM 210: Description of the Flow Processing Unit Using Iverson's Program Notation (G. Shimabukuro), 1962 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - ETM 211: Arithmetic Operation on Field With Imbedded Decimal Point (G. Shimabukuro), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - ETM 212: Multi-Process Data Processor (George T. Shimabukuro), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - ETM 213: Business Data Processing by Telephone (D. N. MacDonald), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - ETM 214: Data Transmission (G. Shimbukuro), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - ETM 216: An Approach to Computer Instructions (G. Shimbukuro), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - ETM 217: Design of Tension and Compression Spring with the Aid of the B220 Computer (Karl Keilstein), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - ETM 218: Dimensioning Analysis via Tolerance Control (Dan Nesin), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - ETM 219: Biax Read Mostly Memories (J. Reese Brown, Jr.), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - ETM 221: Application of Integrated Circuits to B3000 (J. F. Kalbach), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - ETM 222: Report on TTU Cleaning Solvent (Harold E. Hass, Daniel J. Nesin), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - ETM 223: B410 BCL/220 Magnetic Tape Control Unit Test (S. Grabl), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - ETM 224: "O" Ring Durability Investigation (Daniel J. Nesin), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - ETM 226: Summary of the course Taken at M.I.T. (Daniel J. Nesin), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - ETM 227: The Complex Dynamic Behavior of Visco-Elastic Rollers (D. J. Nesin), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - ETM 229: Reliabilitnic Product Design (Floyd W. Looschen), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - ETM 230: A Two Transistor Memory Cell (E. S. Lee), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - ETM 231: Two Transistor Associative Cells and Associative Memory Arrays (E. S. Lee), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - ETM 232: "Copy": A content-Programmed Memory Feature for the B5000 ®. V. Bock), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - ETM 233: Dynamic Storage Allocation, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - ETM 234: A Good Scrambling Function Suitable for Hardware (Donald E. Knuth), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - ETM 235: On the Design and Application of Storage Systems ®. S. Barton), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - ETM 236: Study of Look-Ahead; Hierarchical Thin Film Memory (W. W. Parker and James R. Bennett), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - ETM 238: A Proposed Criteria for Buckling within Wound Reels of Magnetic Tape (D. J. Nesin, G. P. Bottlik), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - ETM 239: A Cylindrical Thin Film Memory Array (J. R. Brown, Jr.), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - ETM 240: File Control Organization with Bulk-File Requirements, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - ETM 242: Proposed Visual Displays for Use with the B5000 Computer System (J. R. Brown), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - ETM 243: Electromagnetic Relay Contact Selection and Application (Warren S. Lincoln), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - ETM 245: Clutch Driven Servo System (H. R. Rayfield), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - ETM 247: B141 Paper Tape Reader Type Tests (F. E. Vrtis), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - ETM 248: A Case for Network Data Service (D. N. MacDonald), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - ETM 249: A Flow Chart Compiler - FLOWSY (Glyn Jones), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - ETM 250: Logic Simulation Program (Kenneth C. Kwan), 1964 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - ETM 253: Random Access Equipment Requirements and Future Directions (D. N. MacDonald), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - ETM 254: Reliability Study of a Group of Binary Information Codes (M. L. Biewer), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - ETM 255: The Inquiry Operation System (John Hadlich), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - ETM 256: Introduction to the Organization and Logic of the Hardware and Software of the B2000 Data Processing System (Ton Davidson), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - ETM 257: Some Data Transmission Requirements in United Kingdom (Floyd W. Looschen), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - ETM 258: Approximating Mean Response Time for the Online Banking System ®. B. English), 1, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - ETM 259: Data on Line Systems (J. F. Kalbach), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ETM 260: Status of NPL as of January 1965 (J. F. Kalbach) (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - ETM 261: A Proposal for a Low Cost Visual Display (J. R. Brown, Jr.), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - ETM 262: Analysis of Transmission Requirements for Information Systems ®. B. English), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - ETM 267: Evaluation of Monolithic Circuit Types, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - ETM 268: Data Communication Tests for the Online Banking System ®. B. English), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - ETM 269: Description of the Data Communication Collection for the On-Line Banking System ®. B. English), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - ETM 270: BOSS Burroughs Open Shop System (D. L. Kunker), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - ETM 271: Method for Measuring Interval Speed of Tae on a Magnetic Tape Transport Using a Computer Program (M. I Behr and L. B. Coon), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - ETM 272: Technique for Measurement of Inter-record Gaps Dynamically of a recorded Tape, with a B200 (M. I. Behr and L. B. Coon), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - ETM 273: Report Generator (D. L. Kunker), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - ETM 274: Simulation Techniques at Pasadena (W. W. Parker), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - ETM 275: A Catalog of Specific Simulator computer Programs at Pasadena (W. W. Parker), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - ETM 277: Computer Technique for Determining Lateral Alignment of Read Gaps of a Magnetic Head on a TSU (M. I. Behr), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - ETM 278: Illustrated Summary of Improved Artwork System (N. Combs and S. J. Saklem), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - ETM 279: Cross-Reference, Flow Chart and Document Editing Program (Glyn Jones), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - ETM 280: Sol [symbolic language], 1965 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - ETM 281: Cross Talk in Cables (G. Katragadda), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - ETM 282: Analysis of Magnetic Tape Unit Performance ©. J. Robinson), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - ETM 283: Occurrence of Undetected Errors During Writing On a Tape and a Method for their Prevention (M. I. Behr and C. E. Bickell), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - ETM 284: B2000 Logic Rules (Anderson, Krossa, Lin), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - ETM 285: Random Number Generation by Hardware Instruction (Bennet and Donald E. Knuth), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - ETM 287: Silicon Monoxide Core Gaps for flying Magnetic Heads (E. V. Jennings), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - ETM 289: Dynamic Contact Tester (Henry D. Testasecca), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - ETM 290: Computer Solution of Multiple Reflections on Open Backlane Wires, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - ETM 291: West German Radio Interference Specifications (F. W. Looschen), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - ETM 292: Read Only Memory Development (F. W. Looschen, R. L. Phillips, Feeser), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - ETM 293: Reference list and Introduction to Paint Finishes (S. J. Saklem), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - ETM 295: Shared Disk Problem, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - ETM 297: Multi-System Shared Disk Processing (Al Shore), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - ETM 298: Low Current Drive Core Memory (Louis A. Rivera), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - ETM 302: High speed Multiplexing for Interunit Communications (John Coupland), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - ETM 303: A User's Description of Simulac/ATT1 (A. P. Toth), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - ETM 305: On-Line Banking System Maintenance Doctrine (F. W. Looschen, et. al.), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - ETM 306: Printed Circuit Cards and Connectors (Geza P. Bottlik), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - ETM 307: Design of a Card Edge connector Contact (G Bottlik), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - ETM 310: Two Layer Card Studies (J. Coupland and P. N. Venkatachalam), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - ETM 312: CTL "C" Spec Logic Rules (J. Coupland and P. N. Venkatachalam), 1968 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - ETM 313: Proper Language Processor for Small Systems (Bunker, et. al.), 1968 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - ETM 314: Communication Network Analyzer Program CNAP (Toth), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - ETM 317: Evaluation Function in Engineering (J. S. Murphy), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - ETM 318: Potential New Application Areas for the PLP (J. S. Murphy), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - ETM 319: Person-Centered Processors, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - ETM 320: A Note on the Impact on Binary Circuitry. (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - ETM 324: Functional Desiderata for Burroughs Systems (John Dunshee), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - ETM 328: An Investigation and Evaluation of Increased Throughput on the B5500 Time Sharing System (Lansford and Price), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - ETM 329: B6500 Time Sharing System Simulator (Norman Nielsen), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - ETM 330: Some Views on Input-Output Processing (Alan N. Doering), 1970 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - ETM 332: Radio Interference Measurements on Computer Installations ®. M. Ziegler), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - ETM 333: A Computer Solution to Transmission Line Problems (Laurence P. Flora), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - ETM 335: CTL Gate Modeling (Laurence P. Flora), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - ETM 336: Topological Analysis Reports Generated by the ESPOL Compiler as Modified to Support Software Measurement System (Karl Balke), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - ETM 337: Optimized Method for Multilayer Board Manufacture Performance (Roy Alabana and Dale B. Myers), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - ETM 339: Computer Program for Acoustic Loudness (Robert P. Owen), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - ETM 341: MS-1 Instruction Times (William C. Price), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - ETM 342: Evaluation of a Microprocessor Controlled Peripheral Controller ®. E. Bohn, C. E. Bube), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - ETM 343: The Electrical Resistance of Perforated Sheets (Robert P. Owen), 1974 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - ETM 344: High Speed Interface (B. Bohn, B. Iwasaki, M. Parisi), undated (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
  - ETM 346: B4700 Auerbach Random File Update (P. Russell, G. Eicher, and Blaine D. Gaither), 1975
  - ETM 347: A Simulation Study to Project B480 Auerbach Random File Update Performance (J. Cochran and B. Gaither), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - ETM 348: MS-3 I/O Subsystem Simulation (T. Bruggere and B. D. Gaither), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - ETM 349: MS-1 Associative Register Study (B. Gaither and J. Hughes), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - ETM 350: B1700 Micro Code Static Measurement (J. S. Hughes), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - ETM 351: MS-3 Software Measurement and Analysis (B. D. Gaither), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - ETM 352: The Functional Specification of a Self-Managing I/O Subsystem (T. H. Bruggere), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - ETM 353: The Architecture of a Self-Managing I/O Subsystem (T. H. Bruggere), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - ETM 354: Functional Specifications for Peripheral Controller Processors (T. H. Bruggere), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - ETM 355: MS-3 System Architecture ®. Lansford, et. al.), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - ETM 356: Performance Evaluation and Modeling Bibliography (B. Gaither), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - ETM 357: Interruptible Power System for Bank of Canada (J. F. Kalbach), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - ETM 364: Electrical Characteristic Requirements for Computer Room Raised Floors (J. F. Kalbach), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - ETM 500: Measuring Program Characteristics and System Quality by Applying Optimizer Technology, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - ETM 502: Measuring Dynamic Characteristics of Algoriths with Special Reference to the B6500 MCP. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - ETM 507: Time-Sharing Techniques in the Context of the Burroughs B6500, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - ETM 511: Three Problems with the B9352 Terminal: A User's Comment, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - ETM 514: Program Geometry Studies with the Aid of an Interactive Model, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - ETM 515: Code Listing of the APL Graph Processor Model, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - ETM 518: An Interactive Program for the Analysis of Program Structure, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Engineering Technical Reports
  - ETR #2: Computer Usage in Engineering, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ETR #3: Magnetic Tape for Digital Computers, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - ETR #4: Deposited Nichrome Resistors, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 3)